<books><book><imgPath>clrs.jpg</imgPath><id>8636416171759962</id><name>Introduction To Algorithms</name><author>CLRS</author><issuecost>50</issuecost><genre>Computer Science</genre><text/></book><book><imgPath>atomichabits.jpg</imgPath><id>7103326662314643</id><name>Atomic Habits</name><author>James Clear</author><issuecost>35</issuecost><genre>Self-Help</genre><text>Atomic Habits, a concept popularized by James Clear in his bestselling book of the same name, refers to the transformative power of small, consistent actions in shaping the trajectory of one's life. Clear argues that meaningful change doesn't result from drastic overhauls, but rather from the cumulative impact of tiny habits repeated day in and day out. By focusing on small, manageable adjustments, individuals can build positive habits that compound over time, leading to substantial and lasting improvements. The key lies in the idea that habits are the building blocks of larger achievements, and by mastering the minute details of behavior, individuals can create a foundation for sustained success and personal growth.</text></book><book><imgPath>9781529019292.webp</imgPath><id>7264656281874266</id><name>Shuggie Bain</name><author>Douglas Stuart</author><issuecost>30</issuecost><genre>Literary Fiction</genre><text>Set in a poverty-stricken Glasgow in the early 1980s, Douglas Stuart’s Booker Prize-winning debut is a heartbreaking story which lays bare the ruthlessness of poverty and the limits of love. Agnes Bain has always dreamed of greater things, but when her husband abandons her she finds herself trapped in a decimated mining town with her three children, and descends deeper and deeper into drink. Her son Shuggie tries to help Agnes long after her other children have fled, but he too must abandon her to save himself. Shuggie is different, and he is picked on by the local children and condemned by adults. But he believes that if he tries his hardest he can escape this hopeless place.</text></book><book><imgPath>9781529077155.webp</imgPath><id>5951483027174284</id><name>American Psycho</name><author>Bret Easton Ellis</author><issuecost>35</issuecost><genre>Literary Fiction</genre><text>One of the most controversial and talked-about novels in modern history, American Psycho is the story of Patrick Bateman, a New York City high-flier with a penchant for fine wines, slickly cut suits and brutal murder. As Bateman's obsession with his hedonistic passions comes to a head, he descends into madness, with macabre and darkly comedic repercussions. Read more about the controversial history of American Psycho.</text></book><book><imgPath>9781529077162.webp</imgPath><id>4643702310057634</id><name>Blood Meridian</name><author>Cormac McCarthy</author><issuecost>40</issuecost><genre>Literary Fiction</genre><text>Written in 1985, Blood Meridian is set in the anarchic world opened up by America’s westward expansion. Through the hostile landscape of the Texas–Mexico border wanders the Kid, a fourteen year-old Tennessean who is quickly swept up in the relentless tide of blood. But the apparent chaos is not without its order: while Americans hunt Indians – collecting scalps as their bloody trophies – they too are stalked as prey. Powerful, mesmerizing and savagely beautiful, Blood Meridian is considered one of the most important works in American fiction of the last century.</text></book><book><imgPath>9781529077209.webp</imgPath><id>3174589725702761</id><name>The Line of Beauty</name><author>Alan Hollinghurst</author><issuecost>45</issuecost><genre>Literary Fiction</genre><text>This Booker Prize-winning novel bottles the essence of the 1980s, as the story follows a quest for beauty against a backdrop of politics, greed and friendships turned toxic. When twenty-year-old Nick Guest moves into an attic room in the Notting Hill home of the wealthy Feddens he is innocent of politics and money. But as he is swept up into the Feddens’ world, Nick must confront the collisions between his own desires, and a world he can never truly belong to. Alan Hollinghurst’s writing style is both stripped back and poetic, and its sensitivity makes this book a true standout. </text></book><book><imgPath>9781529077261.webp</imgPath><id>3562668083162113</id><name>White Noise</name><author>Don DeLillo</author><issuecost>50</issuecost><genre>Literary Fiction</genre><text>Jack Gladney is the creator and chairman of Hitler studies at the College-on-the-Hill. This is the story of his absurd life; a life that is going well enough, until a chemical spill from a train carriage releases an ‘Airborne Toxic Event’ and Jack is forced to confront his biggest fear – his own mortality. The combination of social satire and metaphysical dilemma that Don DeLillo uses to expose our rampant consumerism and media saturation makes White Noise an unmissable work of modern fiction. </text></book><book><imgPath>9781035007790.webp</imgPath><id>2211611699625189</id><name>Pride and Prejudice</name><author>Jane Austen</author><issuecost>50</issuecost><genre>Literary Fiction</genre><text>Named one of BBC's 100 Novels That Shaped Our World, a copy of Pride and Prejudice is a worthy addition to any bookshelf. The story shows how the headstrong Elizabeth Bennet and the aristocratic Mr Darcy must have their pride humbled and their prejudices dissolved before they can acknowledge their love for each other. Jane Austen serves up laughs, romance, sharp observations, life lessons and characters that still feel vividly alive today. A universally acknowledged classic.</text></book><book><imgPath>The God of Small Things cover.webp</imgPath><id>1595809922877070</id><name>The God of Small Things</name><author>Arundhati Roy</author><issuecost>55</issuecost><genre>Literary Fiction</genre><text>This Booker Prize-winning novel and 1990s literary sensation follows fraternal twins, Rahel and Estha, in the state of Kerala, India in 1969. Armed only with the invincible innocence of children, they fashion a childhood for themselves in the shade of the wreck that is their family. But when their English cousin and her mother arrive for a Christmas visit, the twins learn that things can change in a day. Covering themes of love, madness and hope, this story uncoils with an agonizing sense of foreboding and inevitability. Yet, readers will not be prepared for what lies at the heart of it. </text></book></books>